When we turn 14 years old, we begin to think more objectively about our parents.
I'm not being strange. You are the one acting that way.
That's the reason why mom pushed you into the wrong marriage.
What? Wrong marriage?
It was the wrong marriage for you.
I live my life the way I want to and work hard.
I didn't know you felt that way about people with bad beginnings.
Your logic is very heartless an cruel.
Can you be free from your so called "logic"?
Do you have the confidence to live like that forever?
Do you think reality will move the way you want it to?
Also, you are someone who loses to reality.
Yes, I lost to reality.
I lost to reality and chose a life according to common sense
That's why right now, it's really hard for me.
I am barely hanging on
Who do you think is having a harder time? Divorcing someone or breaking up with a guy you didn't even marry?
Which do you think is more difficult? Being hurt by others or being hurt by family?
It's hard for all of us. We are surviving in our own way.
According to your standard of common sense, I guess it was karma for me
That was truly unexpected
Were you about to go to bed?
yes
Is your business going alright?
I think it's going to fail.
Not many people visit my homepage.
You can't have the miracle as PSY.
You're being very cranky again.
I came here to give you a job. Will you do it?
Of course I will do it.
I am opening a new restaurant in Busan.
Make a brochure a develop a marketing strategy for it.
That's what I used to do before.
- Are you saying you aren't going to do it?
- I'll do it.
I shouldn't be picky now.
You take every job I offer.
I shouldn't be picky in order to make money for a living.
You think you can do it if you had your own office?
You think running a business is easy?
To make sucessful business with common idea
you need to have a different prospective
and approach than others.
Please stop lecturing me.
I've had enough.
Just tell me if you're hurting. Stop
thinking about it. It will only make it worse.
I'm different from you. I am much stronger and smarter.
Even if you are stronger and smarter, you are still human.
You feel pain.
I know it because I've done it.
Someone like you, with your backround
Your inside is a mess.
Now I can communicate with you.
While dating you, there was someting missing.
I felt that you were blocking me
from coming into your life.
I am happy these days.
Just like you said, I admitted I'm mean
and it makes me feel more at easy.
I don't know why I tried to justify that I am good person.
That's the first symptom, a lack
of affection.
The second symptom is to be a
cool man like yo, isn't it?
Don't look at me like that, who are you trying to seduce?
I got this card. A card so that I
can star over with you.
Do you want to start over with me?
What is that?
For allowing me to do what I want, I gave
my parent's the right to decide my marriage.
I followed through with that marriage.
But the marriage was called off.
I didn't call it off. Young did it.
I was fooled.
I put the blame on my father,
then I made a deal with him.
Now I can marry a woman I love.
So you are saying we should get married?
No. Let's date on the premise
that we'll get married.
Just like a normal man and woman.
How can we meet ordinarily when we aren't ordinary.
I don't think it is a good idea.
Well, you were probably attracted to me as well because you recognized that I grew up in a cold environment.
We were a couple matched by our subconsciousness.
How can we love when our lacking subconsciousness come together? We've already failed once.
Thus, this is a no?
Yeah, a no.
But, what you talked about before. Let's continue on with that.
That? What is that.
Friends.
- Is this because of Jung Hoon?
- No.
There is something.
- No, there is nothing.
No, there is something.
We kissed that day.
Its a relief that you guys didn't sleep together.
- Why?
- I want to kiss you too.
All the kisses you gave me in the past is invalid from now on.
Why are you lying down? You said you wanted to wash up.
I am too lazy.
It must be tiring to go back and forth between Gangnam and Gangbook.
I will wipe your face with a wet towel.
-There is no need.
-No, it's okay.
Mom. I guess it will be just the two of us tonight.
It's bit too crowded for three of us to sleep here. Haeyoon says she will sleep in the study.
Dohyun is not coming home tonight.
You are going to sleep there?
I don't want to sleep in the master bedroom. Brother-in-law used to sleep there.
-Use this.
-You don't like me now.
Well, dislike is dislike. But you shouldn't catch a cold.
- Are you sleeping?
- I'm not sleeping.
- What is this?
- Stay still. I do this well.
I used to wipe Dohyun's face like this when he came home drunk.
He had a sweet life.
Why are you sitting up? I said I will wipe your face for you.
Your hands are still pretty.
Pretty my butt.
You should thank grandmother. If if you had a hard life, you still have a nice skin and you haven't aged.
You're born with it.
You have a good personality.
Why are you talking about personality out of nowhere?
I need to wash up. Wet towels are not enough.
What kind of privilege did I enjoy really?
- What are you doing here?
- Why?
- Sleep inside.
- I want to sleep here.
Can you sleep properly here when you have to go to work tomorrow? You are going to be tired.
- Sleep inside.
- The master bedroom is too small for the three of us.
What do you mean it's too small? We all slept in there before.
Okay! Why are you screaming?
Okay. It's not like anyone gave me credit before.
Children are like that.
But still, kids should give me credit. Shouldn't they?
I gave birth to them. I raised them.
I must have been one of those kids to my mom.
No, I wasn't like that.
What do you mean you weren't like that? You were reluctant spend money for your mom but you felt like you couldn't spend enough money for your kids.
I want to see my mom.
How can it be me? Her mom! Bad girl!
Let's just go home.
We have a lot things to talk about.
We can talk on the phone.
Is the phone the same thing as talking face to face?
- It's different.
- That's what I'm saying.
- When are we getting married?
- When?
I don't like it because it's too sour.
It's not sour, it's sweet.
I don't want it. It's sour. It will be nice to have gimbap now as a snack.
You are picky.
Should we get married next week?
Are you crazy?
- I'm good with it.
- Really? You are good with it?
Yes.
- There is nothing impossible when the two of us are together.
- There is nothing impossible!
- It really isn't sour.
- Not this.
- Come to the restaurant tomorrow.
- I don't want to go back to the past.
I know.
But, I don't know how to form a relationship with a person.
Till now, I just catered to everyone's preferences like a dumb person
I hid myself to be considered as being nice.
But it shouldn't be.
No, it shouldn't be so.
I think the best thing for the both of us is to break up.
It might be so, but it might not be so.
There is worth in getting back together.
I guess I was born as a dumb person.
I don't know how to say no to you.
We are subconsciously connected
I think our love starts from now on.
I always thought both of our parent's interference was giving us a hard time when we were preparing for our wedding.
It wasn't that.
You and I were the problem.
The biggest hurdles were the problems we ourselves had
Problems, solutions... yourself.
I think all of these feel empty.
I want to see you.
Unnie, you came?
Why are you making sushi?
I was gonna bring it to Minho. You like it as well too.
Did you cry?
- No I didn't.
- Your eyes are swollen.
It looks like you didn't sleep. Did you not sleep?
-No
-You look haggard, as if you didn't have any sleep.
When are you going to get married. Do it quickly since you have already decided to get married.
I was going to do that. It's next week.
That fast? How are you going to prepare?
I will do everything myself. Don't worry.
Tofu stew, he doesn't have parents?
He said all his family members are in the United States.
His mother lives with his older brother.
He said he is the only one in Korea.
Then there will be no need for wedding presents.
No, there is no need to worry about wedding presents.
I am moving into Minho's place.
How are you having a marriage that I wanted for my children?
It turned out that way. Where is Haeyoon?
She will go to work from her sister's place.
You didn't bring her here? How is she supposed to come here by herself?
It would be hard for her to leave for work in the morning.
Going to work or not, it's her business.
-Why do you talk as if she's a stranger
-No, I don't want it.
It's tasty. Why is she being like that?
I'm tired.
My house is the best.
It's my loss if I don't eat or sleep.
I'll go to work after waking up.
Aren't you going to school?
- What time is it?
- Seven thirty.
- What about mom?
- She left.
She said she has to open up the store early.
How can she leave by herself? She has to care for me.
You only look for mom when you need her.
I'm sorry. I did wrong yesterday.
What did you do wrong? Does your common sense change overnight?
-That's how your common sense is
-I thought you would understand me.
-You are one of mom's victims.
-I never thought I was mom's victim.
On the contrary. Thanks to mom, I was able to live a life I dreamt about.
and realized how foolish I was to have that kind of dream life.
I was jealous of you because you're smart, pretty, and knew what you were doing.
But, like what mom said, you're only outwardly smart.
There is no drama in your life.
Once you realize real life is full of drama, you learn what living a life is.
Don't judge my life when you don't know what you're talking about.
Don't blame mom for breaking up with Junghoon.
Your relationship was only that strong.
It's because you two learned about life from a book.
I think I need to go to school even though I'm late.
-Here is the cabbage soup that you like.
-Thank you.
Yes, Unnie.
I set up a blind date for Junghoon.
What blind date?
Are you going to leave him alone like that? He is going to age and die as an unmarried man.
Why do you say such things?
Tongjin enterprises. It's a medium sized enterprise, but it's a very solid company. The parents are nice too.
She is much better than the other girl Jung Hoon was going to marry.
It's not hard to come across such a girl.
Do you think he will go on a blind date now?
You can't even control you child to be dragged by his will?
Alright, I'll ask him at least.
He would of course say he would go if you ask him.
I'll tell you the time and place. Just send him out.
Unnie.
What's wrong?
My older sister wants Junghoon to go on a blind date.
How can he go to a blind date? It has not even been that long since he broke up.
That's what I'm saying.
- Don't tell Jung Hoon.
- Don't you think it's alright to at least ask him?
No.
Like unnie said, we can't leave him like that.
I don't love that fact that he spends a lot of time with Dongbi.
He would take care of it himself.
But...
-I am a bit disappointed.
-Why?
I feel like you are only concerned about Jung Hoon.
No, I'm not. To me, you are my number one.
I think I lost that first place to Jung Hoon.
Look at me. If you focus on me, you can reduce the concern for Jung Hoon.
You are a greedy person.
Why are you coming in?
Why don't you go on a blind date?
Aunt says she specially arranged a meeting for you.
She says she is pretty and nice.
Why? Why do you look at me like that?
Do you think I would want to go on a blind date?
That's what I told your aunt, but your aunt...
Tell her I am not going to go. Tell her not to be concerned about that from now on.
-It's too good to pass up.
-I am a bit disappointed.
- About what?
- About you.
How did my mom become like this?
- Hey!
- I'll get going.
Unnie, let's have that meeting. Like you said, I don't think he should be left like that.
We have the results of home visit investigation and we have a problem.
I'm sorry for making you come when you are busy.
- I have to fit your busy schedule.
- Sit down.
Yes.
So the home visit investigation is completed?
Home visit investigation is completed and I saw the report.
Take a look.
In general, the report is positive.
Where is the section for home visit investigator's opinion?
Home visit investigator's opinion section is not open for viewing.
I could only make copies excluding that section.
Then, there is no way for me to know the opinion of the investigator.
So there is no way for me to know who will have the parental right and custody.
In these cases, the mom will almost always have the parental right and custody of the child.
The child is seven years old.
Then, putting custody aside,
can I at least have the parental right?
Parental right and the custody go hand in hand.
when the child goes to school, the parent with parental right has to reside on the same address with the kid.
Otherwise, it will be inconvenient for the parent with custody.
If Hyejin gets the parental right, can she change the child's last name if she were to remarry?
No. She needs to file a case to change the last time
and it could only be changed if the biological father agrees to it.
The mom cannot change the child's last name at will just because she has the parental right.
That's a relief.
Is there any way that I can have custody?
How is the law so unfair for the father?
Is the mother the only one who can raise a child well?
It's better for the father to raise the son.
I told you before. I am persistent.
There is a way.
What problem arose?
We are not allowed to make copies of the home visit investigator's opinion section.
When our employee went to make copies, she made copies of the opinion section when the clerk was distracted.
Look at the last page.
The plaintiff has high income and high intellectual ability
He can make a good environment for the child.
It says it's okay to give the custody to the father.
It says, the custody doesn't have to go to the mother Jung Hyejin.
Then, to sum it up...
Before, you had a sure advantage over your husband. But based on the home visit investigator's report. your position is similar to that of your husband's now.
-I can never give the custody.
-Your husband feels the same way.
If your husband really fights for it, the custody might fall in his hands.
Shouldn't custody of a 7 year old fall in the hands of the mom?
There is no such thing as a given. We have to take it from him by winning.
Then what should we do?
Well, the good thing is only we know the opinion of the investigator.
Your husband doesn't know it. If he did, he will be full of it.
Won't they find out sooner or later?
They won't go that far, since it's not common to do so.
Instead, they will try to come up with countermeasures to get the custody.
What kind of countermeasure?
We will apply for the child's psychiatric evaluation.
Using this psychiatric evaluation, we will stress the father son bond,
and find fault's with mom's way of raising the child.
When will we do that?
Since home visit investigation is over,
a date for the second step will be scheduled.
You could request the psych evaluation to the judge then.
Since Nam Dohyun isn't aware of the advantage they have
they will request the child psychiatric evaluation to get the custody.
Evaluate Taewon
Isn't this too much for the child?
They are not gonna ask him "Do you want to live with mom or dad?". So you don't have to be worried.
But we have to solidify our position then. Taewon needs his mom.
In the second preparation process, we could look over the verification that we requested
and the next step may be expedited.
or it could be passed over to the home investigation deparment.
Build a sense of closeness with the child.
Play with your child often.
Then you could overcome any disadvantage in the psychiatric evaluation.
Alright.
Since you're already here, should I work on your laugh line with some injection?
- That would be good.
- Can you wait outside?
- I'll prepare it.
- Thank you.
It's tasty. It is very different from what they sell.
I think you have a preference. You don't eat any sushi.
It's disgusting. Eat it with a chopstick.
I washed my hands.
Even if you wash your hands often, bacteria gets on it very quickly.
Can't I live with some bacteria?
Alright, let's live with some bacteria too.
Oh, where should we have our wedding ceremony?
Do you want to have a wedding ceremony?
I don't want to have a wedding ceremony, but I heard for women, their dream is to wear a wedding dress.
I don't have dreams like that.
Don't regret later that you didn't do what others did.
I really don't like that sort of thing. Getting married in a wedding dress at a wedding hall like everyone else.
How do you want to do it then?
I don't want to have a wedding ceremony.
Let's just register the marriage and live together.
And let's eat with the family.
- Can we do that?
- Yes, we can.
Then I would really appreciate it. I didn't want to have a wedding ceremony again.
That's why we shouldn't do it.
- There is nothing about you that I dislike.
- Me too.
There is nothing about you that I dislike as well.
I have one! This.
-Should I not do it?
-Go ahead.
It's tasty.
Hello, I was a little late.
It's alright. You are busy if you are a CEO.
How am I a CEO when I don't have any employees?
Aunt, sit next to Minho.
Our story can be made into an article?
Yes. You guys met when you are 50 years old and 43 years old. Both love riding the motorcycle.
Beauty and the best. Soulmate. I could spin it in many different ways.
Are you giving us money for the interview?
We should be grateful that we are featured in a magazine.
Aunt, you're the best!. Minho. Even though you're loaded, it seems like you're growing stingy after you decided to get married.
Please invest in my magazine. It's gonna get shut down at this rate.
Look who's talking. I've heard the traffic to your site in increasing and the you have been receiving positive response for the video clips.
It doesn't lead to earnings. Well, both of you, please stand up for picture.
One, two, three!
Congratulations on your marriage, aunt.
Uncle...
- It feels weird that you are calling me uncle.
- Isn't it better than ahjussi?
It is better.
Are you really not going to have a wedding ceremony?
Yes, I am not going to go on a honeymoon.
What are you going to do after registering the marriage?
We will have a family dinner and move into Minho's place right after.
To live together at his place, I have to change some things to make it feel like our place.
But leaving out travelling is not that great.
Dongbi. I've always wanted to try living with a guy.
We can go travelling whenever we want while living together.
Honeymoon seems so old fashioned.
-What did you older sister say?
-She told me to do whatever I want.
One good thing about aging is you don't really care about what others think.
Everyone pretty much leaves us alone to do whatever we want.
She says it is a relief that we met at our age.
That's correct. I'm not going to get married until when I am fifty.
- Do you think that's easy?
- I don't think it's impossible from how it is right now.
- You came?
Where have you been?
I am busy with the Busan branch and all.
Busan is a foreign city to me. Even the way the speak, it's different.
You punk, I should just do away with you(in Busan dialect)
What? you punk, just do...?
- Do you think anyone can do it?
- It sounds like alien language.
- See me after work.
- Alright.
Please have fun.
His height is definitely gorgeous.
I thought you don't like him.
Hating him and his height are different.
Are you guys meeting again?
Next week, over the weekend, we can have a family meeting, right?
If you want. Why, will the parents have a meeting before the wedding?
What parent meeting? I was planning on having a wedding reception here.
- You are getting married next week on the weekend?
- Yes.
It's very fast.
In this world, marriage is better when it happens faster.
You still haven't made up with Haeyoon?
She's having a hard time.
I had a hard time too.
I know. You should have told others about what happened to your brother. Why do you keep it to yourself?
It must have been really hard for you.
Thank you. You're the best.
Haeyoon even went to file a missing persons report when you went MIA.
Her anger is understandable.
You should have at least picked up.
I didn't have roaming service abroad. I only listened her voicemail later.
You could have said that.
You have Junghoon and Kijoong by your side.
There is no one by Haeyoon's side.
I know how it feels like to have nobody around you.
I set up a meeting between Haeyoon and Junghoon. But it seems like they really broke up.
That was it.
Mom: I am at the coffee shop. Meet me after work.
Where are you, I don't see you.
I'm sorry, I lied.
What?
There is a girl named Kim Saebyeon at the coffee shop. She's your blind date.
Since your aunt is setting you up, please be polite even if you don't feel like it.
-Mr. Ha Junghoon?
-Yes?
-Did you just get off work?
-Yes.
I came her to save time since I thought it would be even later if we met at the city center.
If I don't like my date, I prefer to meet early and part ways quickly.
I'm sorry, I think there was a mistake.
I didn't come on my will. I came because It thought my mother came.
So?
I'm telling you because I thought you would be uncomfortable.
I don't feel uncomfortable. It's rush hour right now so there is a lot of traffic.
Let's talk while we wait it out.
You really must have nothing to do.
Lately, I have been your household butler. Your sister, your mom, and you are my last stop.
I wanted to see you anyways concerning our family's business.
Yes, don't hide your feelings now.
You're cheesy. Stop it.
Do you want to eat something spicy? The cheesiness will go away.
I am saying your presence is cheesy.
- How should I solve that problem?
- I'm cold.
That can be solved by getting in the car. Let's go.
- I know now.
- What?
If I liked you in the past.
I forgot why since it's so long ago.
Why did you like me?
I think you were a problem solver.
You always gave me a solution to a problem...
For problems without a solution, we considered it as something nonexistent.
That's right.
But oppa, I think problems without a solution are the ones that have value.
Did you tell my mom that I broke up because of her?
Yes.
How could you say something like that.
How can you say that to her face?
Your mother needs to know that she is an obstacle to her children.
It hurts now, but thinking about tomorrow, that's better.
Tomorrow? I could still hold it together now. What tomorrow?
There is only tomorrow if I survive today.
There still will be tomorrow. You're mom is the problem.
- I have confidence that I can solve the problem.
- I love my mom.
She may not seem to make sense in other people's eyes and in my eyes as well.
But what can I do when she is my mom?
That guy. He won't try to solve my mom. He will accept her as she is.
With me.
That is why I let him go.
He is nice. He is too nice.
Don't consider my mom as a problem to be solved. It's offensive.
- I understand.
- Don't come find me.
Even if I come find you, just don't follow me.
You can always deny me anytime anywhere.
Even if I come in front of the school, you just have to go home.
But you come along with me. Which means you like me back. But you tell me to stop coming to see you. Then, do you think I will listen?
You are correct about that. I wanted to talk about my mom today.
- Since we are done, let's go.
- Let's do that.
Nothing gets through to her. I was just saying it but she left for real.
How was today? Unnie said that she is a nice person.
I'm supressing my emotions so that I don't lose my temper.
You really are too much.
What do you mean I am too much?
Even though I may have gone against your wishes, you're being too rude.
I told you I don't want to go on a blind date. Why are you ignoring me?
Because you are being like this, I gave you a chance to meet someone new.
You don't have to date her. You could just talk to her.
How can I hold a conversation with her when I haven't seen her before?
Even puppies have feelings and don't do things they don't feel like doing. When I asked to be left alone, did that seem like a joke to you?
Joke? Is that the way to speak to your mom?
If you want to be respected, please respect my words too.
Why do you ignore your sons words and still want to be respected?
Because you only know Hye Yoon, there are other pretty ladies out there...
Do you think I am not dating other pretty girls because I don't know anyone prettier than Hye Yoon?
I can't get through to you.
Can't get through to me?
I set up the blind date, knowing you will rebel like this. But it was for you.
How can you have no understanding for your mother?
Why don't you have a understanding for me?
Honey, look at him. Did you hear what he said to me?
Please stop mom. Does it make sense she's setting up blind date for me at this point?
-Hey! Ha Junghoon!
-Please leave him alone.
Have I done such wrong for him to raise his voice like that?
So you made him go on the blind date after all?
If you criticize me too, I can't stand it.
-I got it
-That mean punk.
He should acknowledge my intentions were good even though it didn't lead to a good end.
Why aren't you comforting me?
I can't really come up with anything to say in a situation like this.
Honey!
-What are you doing here?
-Let me spend the night here
What are you doing here?
I have no food at my house. He said he would give me food so I came.
If someone offers food, you would even go with the human traffickers.
What's wrong with you?
I'm going to go crazy because of my mom and my aunt.
Why is my mom included in it?
I had to go on a blind date because of aunt. What's wrong with her?
It's because she's bored. Kihyun used to hang out with her. But he's abroad now.
- Why are you letting her be?
- I got divorced recently.
How is that a divorce if you didn't even live with her?
-I was totally humiliated.
-My engagement fell apart.
But why is mom like that? She's being incondierate.
I saw your mother recently before, but she is scary.
Are you talking bad about my mom?
Do you want to see some pasta?
Are you guys back together?
Why are you curious about that? Do you want us to get back together?
I want you guys to break up.
Why?
I want all the couples in the world to break up.
Since Christmas is coming up, single people are going nuts. I better get going.
Who is going to do the dishes? You should wash the plates you ate on.
- You should clean it up for me.
- Why should I?
You are my friend. Can't a friend do something like that?
-Please set up a deadline for the brochure
-Got it.
It's cold, I'm not going out.
It's not like you ever saw me out. You shouldn't act different.
-Bye
-Spend the night at your place.
-Don't sleep away from home
-Take care of yourself.
Honey, don't let him drink, he becomes a dog.
Hey!
You killed my heart.
From now on, whom can I trust to befriend them?
Whom can I trust to fall in love?
At least text me saying you're alright even if you are travelling. I won't be friends with you if you don't.
- Here.
- What is it?
It's a wedding present.
I bought it when we went to Poland last time. It's interesting.
It's pretty.
I heard you aren't wearing a wedding dress. Put it on the clothing you wear when you go register your marriage.
Thank you.
- You are here.
- Aunt!
- Was there something between you two?
- No.
Hye Jin said she is sleeping here today.
She came her to spend the night since it's hard on your mother to go back and forth.
That's good.
Why are you so indifferent about it?
Your mom is acting weird too. She's cooped up in her room.
It feels awkward. I hate this sort of atmosphere.
I am going in.
Don't go it yet. Since we are all here, let's go out for a bachelorette party
I'm getting married next week.
I don't feel like it. I will stay with Taewon.
-We can't leave anyone out.
-I will watch over Taewon, you go Haejin.
You guys are too much.
What are you looking at?
Mom, what are you doing?
I'm calculating.
Aunt says we should go to karaoke.
Karaoke?
She wants us to throw her a bachelorette party since she's getting married next week.
Bachelorette party my butt.
Let's all go out. It's been a while.
No, I don't want to. It's cold outside.
Unnie, let's go!
- I'm not going.
- Let's go!
Let's go. Take a hold of your mom.
Everyone! I am getting married! Thank you unnie!
Haejin, Haeyoon, I love you.
Unnie, thank you! I'm getting married.
Aigoo, she hasn't grown up yet.
I guess it's good that she she hasn't grown up yet. She has the best life out of all of us.
-She is.
-She is really.
Minho, I love you.
It's your turn, unnie.
-I don't want to.
-Madame Lee to the floor.
Man is really tiresome for woman
I got the party going and you're dragging the mood down.
You liven up the mood.
Hurry!
Unnie, those two are weird.
I think they had a fight.
That's why you married a wrong person because you were controlled by mom.
Let's go hom now.
Why are you all being like this?
It's not fun.
Before, you were singing, melancholic and all
-Let's go for a second round
-You really want the whole deal.
I need to go check on Taewon.
Teacher Lee will take good care of him. Don't worry about it. Let's go. I want french fries.
- I don't want to.
- Let's go.
I'm a happy virus. I'll share my energy.
I feel like everyone is on a race to be the most unhappy.
Especially you, Haeyoon. You're the youngest.
Just because I'm young doesn't mean my pains are young as well, aunt.
Aunt, she always says its only hard for her.
In my view, she looks like she is the most comfortable.
It's because I learned life through books. It's weak and lame.
Why are you being touchy about it?
Hyejin keeps on being like that from before.
I am not being like this for no reason.
Then am I being like this for no reason? As if I am not in pain?
Why are you in such pain?
It hurts, it is hard, I feel like dying.
I almost married the guy I had been dating for 3 years. Then we broke up.
I am unhappy.
I'm divorcing my husband who I lived with for seven years.
It is also through court. While he was living with me, there wasn't just one or two girls.
He's dying to take the custody and he cut off all financial support.
The custody that I thought was a given, is no longer so. I may not be able to raise my own child.
You are more unhappy than I am?
Win for Haejin.
It is too early to say who is the winner.
A daughter that I raised for twenty eight years goes running around in the neighborhood saying she is embarrased of me.
She also says she broke up because of me. Because I am uncommon sensical.
-You mean you lack common sense.
-I know too.
It's a joke.
Uncommon sensical. Rather than lacking common sense. Uncommon sensical seems more sophisticated
I couldn't even act like I know what's going on because I was trying to keep up a front.
I am not scared of anything in the world.
It was a scary when my child said I am embarassing.
I wanted to argue it out with you but I wasn't sure what you would say. So I was holding it in.
But as you know, I am not the type to hold it in.
I'm sorry, mom.
Don't just say those word. Let's really talk about it.
Okay, then. I will be honest.
You contradict yourself.
You change your stance depending on the situation and act whatever serves you well. You're not consistent.
Let's talk about my wedding. You did a background check on my in-laws.
Marriage comes from the idea of men and women being equal.
But you say that the man has to take care of the money.
How can it be equality when we're not on equal footing financially?
Who says that men and women are equal? Who says people are equal?
If everyone is equal, why am I living like this?
Is it actually equal if it is written in the book? It is only thought of as equal on a test paper.
Were you guys talking about stuff like this without me?
This is news to me. You all left me out?
You left us out. You're happy.
I'm saying this now, but...
I didn't want to come home because there was a dark shadow cast over the house.
I feel personally betrayed but that wench there.
What is wrong with me? Although I can't be considered an awesome mom, aren't I close to being one?
I tried to make her happy.
Tried to make it work with Junghoon.
I even presented lipstick to Junghoon's mom. Running from place to place.
I am saying that's not according to common sense. How old am I? I am 28 years old.
I have a job too.
When it's over between a man and a woman why do the parents get involved? It's between the two of them.
Then you take care of it yourself. I am not holding you back.
And then when something comes up, you take hold.
It's my personality! What can I do about it. When something comes up my body naturally responds.
That's what I am saying. I deal with you because you're my mom. Why drag another person into this?
Let the family just live together.
Hye Jin, tell me. Am I that weird?
Isn't she the weird one?
In here, who thinks I don't have common sense?
You are the only one!
Who thinks Hye Yoon doesn't have common sense?
Look here. We are split one to one.
Amazing. How can I win an argument with you?
If you can't win in a argument with your theory, why go against me?
You are the one who is wrong.
After hearing those words from you, I thought about it for several days, going through sadness like you can't believe.
No matter how much I think about it, for you Jung Hoon is the perfect man.
Mom!
He is the only one who can accept your harsh personality.
- Are you done?
- Jung Hoon likes you.
What?
I met him recently. He told me to call him whenever.
He says he would come if I called.
- That means he likes you.
- Yes, it means he likes her.
That's what I am saying. That girl thinks I am weird.
Others think I am a good person. Knowing what's right and wrong.
It's fine as long as Junghoon likes me. I thought you are not able to get married because of me.
I broke up with him because he's willing to cope with everything for me.
He is that kind of man.
Where are you going in the middle of the conversation?
Washroom!
My goodness, having a daughter without common sense is so frustrating.
It feels good that you are taking it like this, mom.
About what?
I was worried that you will get upset if you find out about this.
I am a proud person.
I flipped my thought process. I gave birth to her and raised her with the money that I earned.
I have nothing to lose.
You are right. You have nothing to lose.
I feel all better now. Finally able to digest my food.
What is going to happen with you and Dong Bi.
We decided to get together again.
Do well this time.
We are cautious not to become like the old times.
Don't hurt Dongmi anymore. Date her with marriage in mind
- You talk as if you are her guardian.
- I'm her friend.
You guys are still friends after what you guys went through?
I will get rid of all my female friends before I get married. Don't worry
You said you would sleep over.
I think it is correct to sleep in one place.
Thinking of Hye Yoon, I think I have to live properly.
That way I would feel better when I date her again
You're quite something. If I had that kind of willpower, I will get back with her
I won't do that. When I am dating Hyeyoon again, we cannot go back to the kind of relationship we had
You surprised me!
Why are over there like that?
- I'm sorry.
- You are at least good at self reflecting.
I'm telling you I'm sorry.
I was pushy.
I think you are becoming more like aunt because you spend more time with her.
I am nervous
why are you nervous?
To me it doesn't seem like you broke up with Hyeyoon
I acted like that to help you end it for good.
Why do you hate Hye Yoon so much?
The two families are worlds apart (in terms of financial stability, etc.)
Before, I didn't look for things like this.
Ha Junghoon, you know that I liked Hyeyoon before I got to know her family
So?
I changed my mind during the wedding preparation process. You need to consider the spouse's family as well.
Look at Haeyoon's mom. There is no stopping her.
Then, according to you, what kind of family suits well with our family then?
Well, a family of scholars, both parents are alive.
The priest preaches every week then we shouldn't judge based on appearances.
That's low. Attacking on faith.
I realized this in the wedding preparation process. If I cannot handle my mom, I will just give up on marriage altogether.
What?
Don't just blame Haeyoon's mother only. It takes two to tango.
You're a bit much.
Maybe, you are worse than Haeyoon's mother.
You received a higher education than Haeyoon's mother, grew up in a wealthy family. Father loves you very much.
Shouldn't you be better?
You're asking to be spanked.
Dongbi.
Can you come out right now?
I don't think we have a reason to meet.
Seeing how you picked up the phone, you are feeling a bit of regret as well.
Here.
What is it?
You will know when you see it.
I'm going to be home.
Junghoon, Hyeyoon Congratulations on the marriage!
Congrats on the marriage, you punks
It's been three years since I became witness to love between you two
Jung Hyeyoon, I am jealous of you
Because you have a guy besides you who will take all your bad temper
I introduced him to you. So you have to be good to me forever
Hi Hyeyoon
Sit properly.
I did sit properly.
Imagine it's been 10 years since you got married and say how that feels
Our kid is already in elementary school
You are still pretty.
thin and you still make my heart flutter
how cheesy, I am gonna delete this clip, say something else
When will you interview Haeyoon? I will copy that after watching it.
Please learn how to be on your own. On your own!
I mad this to give you after your wedding
I am giving you a preview even though it's still incomplete
If I had to choose between either you or Jung Hoon...
I will choose you. Since your'e my best friend. There is only one best
I am sorry Hyeyoon. I miss you
Welcome.
You b**ch. I don't know how to forgive you
Do you know how hard it was for me then?
After I broke up with Junghoon, I was worried about possible pregnancy
I was abandoned by my parents for more than 10 years and my younger brother committed suicide
We cannot objectively judge on sadness
considering what we had to go through, what happened to me was a more serious matter
On top of that, I saw you two.
You knew that it was nothing even if you saw.
Are you someone who wouldn't know?
I had clothes on.
You know Junghoon's facial expression, the way how he talks, and his behavior. Is he the type to be able to hide anything? He's a simple guy and everything shows
You just wanted to find a stronger excuse to break up with him
You guys were lying on the same bed.
I'm sorry about that. I did that because I didn't want to sleep on the floor because my back hurt.
He had the bed first.
We can't become friends again.
Then why did you come?
I don't have any friends.
I am now able to look inside my heart...
I need somebody to talk to.
But I don't have that someone.
Will you become my friend again?
I was on the internet all the time
I wanted to talk but I had no one
I'm surfing the internet all the time. I talk with the internet.
The internet is my friend.
I can't even eat with it or fight with it. You bad girl
Hi Dongbi.
Let's go. We have another witness coming
He is here.
does it have to be him?
- Alright.
- Do you not like it?
Let's go hyung. Aunt
It's ready. Wait, a picture
1, 2, 3
it's a bit boring. It's your wedding. You are not even kissing each other?
no
Where are you off to?
wedding reception
You are just going to the wedding reception only and not the wedding ceremony?
They didn't have a ceremony, they are just having reception only
It's only one wedding in their lifetime, the bride must not like it
That was what the bride wanted. I'll be back
okay
It's been a while. I guess you're avoiding me
Yes because I am a little sorry.
It's so weird how I don't hate my kids. If you were a stranger, I would not want you in my sight
I feel the same way too
After aunt gets married, you give it some thought too
You like Jung Hoon.
I don't know why you keep talking about Jung Hoon.
I thought you didn't like him when I was dating him
You only know if he was a gold or poop (its value) after the relationship is over
It's been over. He's a gold
If I was the reason for the break up, I'll disappear.
Don't talk non sense.
You know how I keep my words
I will be gone
No need
I could do that for my kids. I will be gone
Let's just get going. We'll be late to the reception
Stand here together, I'll take a family photo.
I'll be taking the picture.
How about dad?
Dad!
You are part of our family too.
You should come here too.
I'll take the picture again. One, two, three.
- You came?
- Yes.
Hello mother
oh, are you here with someone?
with Minho
Oh
My Hyeyoon
Are you doing well?
yea
you two go over there and not be in the way
- Should I get you something to drink?
- It's alright.
- Did you cut your hair again?
- No, I didn't.
It looks a little shorter.
You really must have lost some interest in me. Not even noticing my hairstyle.
Thank you for attending wedding reception for Chang Minho and Yoon Deulrae.
-That sounds so formulaic.
-I've never done this before.
Since this is my first time, please understand if I am a bit green.
That sounds formulaic as well
-Dohyun, come out. You do it.
-This is a bit weird.
-No, you go ahead and do it
-What is?
-The wedding reception is a bit weird.
The witness to our wedding is about to have his 2nd divorce,
The one who's hosting the wedding was divorced on the day of his wedding,
-it's a bit weird.
-What about the husband?
He has been married twice. It all fits together.
That's true too.
Here comes the bride and the groom.
The bride looks as pretty as her age.
Like a 28 year old.
Minho looks happy.
Than you. This is my third marriage.
It is my first marriage.
Every time I got married, I promised I would live with them forever.
In this marriage, there is no promise like that.
I would only love her today and live like that.
Next, Lady Lee Deulja will speak on behalf of the family.
If I knew this was coming, I would prepared a speech.
Enjoy your meal. Food is the most important thing in wedding reception.
- I don't know if this restaurant's food tastes good.
- It tastes good.
That's what the owner of the restaurant thinks.
I am the older sister of Lee Deulrae. Just in case some people might get confused that I am her mother since I am speaking on behalf of the family.
To be honest, I am not interested in this marriage.
Interest is something that you have if you are worried.
It's obvious that they will live well together so what is there to be interested about?
Ha Jung Hoon!
When will you get married? When will you marry Haeyoon?